

CONTACT

- andres.orozco.dev@gmail.com
- (+1) 631-459-8183
- Miami, Fl
- Work authorization in USA | COL
- Github
- LinkedIn

ABOUT ME

Systems Engineer who loves code and good practices, since 2020 I started in Frontend development with two years of experience in languages such as HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript, using frameworks and libraries such as Angular, React and Bootstrap. In 2023 I started to discover Python 3 and its FastAPI web framework, which motivates me to be a constant learner and a true believer in teamwork.

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native

English: Intermediate

Andres F. Orozco

Systems Engineer | Frontend Developer | Python Developer

WORK HISTORY

Software Developer (Sistecredito S.A.S.)

Decembre 2021 - March 2022 (Medellin, Col)

• Building and maintaining web applications in Python.

Middle Software Developer (Sistecredito S.A.S.)

Decembre 2021 - March 2022 (Medellin, Col)

• Building and maintaining web applications in Angular.

Junior Software Developer (Sistecredito S.A.S.)

July 2020 - November 2021 (Medellin, Col)

• Building and maintaining web applications in Angular.

Apprentice of Systems engineering (Multimedia Lab.)

January 2020 - July 2020 (Medellin, Col)

 Building and maintaining web applications in Angular - React -React Native - Wordpress.

EDUCATION

2021 Bachelor's Degree in Systems Engineering Universidad de Medellin.

SKILLS

